/* create obj start */
let question_obj = [
    {"question":"Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges",
        "option": ["Narmada","Mahanadi","Son","Netravati"],
        "answer": "Narmada"
    },
    {"question":"The Central Rice Research Station is situated in",
        "option": ["Chennai","Cuttack","Bangalore","Quilon"],
        "answer": "Cuttack"
    },
    {"question":"Who among the following wrote Sanskrit grammar",
        "option": ["Kalidasa","Charak","Panini","Aryabhatt"],
        "answer": "Panini"
    },
    {"question":"Which among the following headstreams meets the Ganges in last",
        "option": ["Alaknanda","Pindar","Mandakini","Bhagirathi"],
        "answer": "Bhagirathi"
    },
    {"question":"The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is",
        "option": ["Zinc","Silver","Copper","Aluminum"],
        "answer": "Silver"
    },
    {"question":"Patanjali is well known for the compilation of",
        "option": ["Yoga Sutra","Panchatantra","Brahma Sutra","Ayurveda"],
        "answer": "Yoga Sutra"
    },
    {"question":"River Luni originates near Pushkar and drains into which one of the following",
        "option": ["Rann of Kachchh","Arabian Sea","Gulf of Cambay","Lake Sambhar"],
        "answer": "Rann of Kachchh"
    },
    {"question":"Which one of the following rivers originates in Brahmagiri range of Western Ghats",
        "option": ["Pennar","Cauvery","Krishna","Tapti"],
        "answer": "Cauvery"
    },
    {"question":"The country that has the highest in Barley Production",
        "option": ["China","India","Russia","France"],
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {"question":"Tsunamis are not caused by",
        "option": ["Hurricanes","Earthquakes","Undersea landslides","Volcanic eruptions"],
        "answer": "Hurricanes"
    },
];

let answer_obj = [];

/* create obj end */

